Guide to the Robert Kraushaar papers, [ca. 1970-1990]
Kraushaar, Robert papers
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Photocopy of Leeds City Council Report "Economic and Industrial Development in the City"
- 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  (Full Report) Greater London Regional Council of the Labour Party; GLC Election 1981; Report of the Industry and Employment Working Party
- March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  "The Future Role and Organisation of Local Government: Functional Study No. 6" - INLOGOV Economic Development
- 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  "Prospectus 1981/82" - The Network of Labour, Community Research and Resource Centres
- Fainstein, Susan S.. "Urban Transformation and Economic Development Planning", October 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Printout of paper presented at the annual meeting of the Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning, Buffalo, New York, October 27-30, 1988: 19 pages
- Fainstein, Susan S. & Norman. "The Ambvalent State: The Role of U.S. Subnational Governments in Economic Development", August 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Printout of paper presented at the meeting of the Internaional Sociological Association Research Committee on Regional and Urban Development, Eleventh World Congress of Sociology, New Delhi, India, August 18-22, 1986: 18 pages
- Various. Various Papers and Working Papers on Economic Development, November 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Memo to Western Societies Program from Susan Christopherson, Pierre Clavel, and Margaret Wilder
- September 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Urban Governance and Industrial Decline: The Politics of Transformation; Birmingham UK, Detroit and Sheffield 1980-1996" - Paul Lawless, Alan DiGaetano, Robin Boyle
- 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Green Community Project" - Author Unknown, 4 pages
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Urban Industrial Development Policy Making In Comparative Perspective" - Kraushaar peer review of preliminary submission by DiGaetano, Boyle, and Lawless
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Single-Industry Towns and Industrial Development Policy Making in Comparative Perspective" - Alan DiGaetano, Robin Boyle, Paul Lawless
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Some Notes on Local Economic and National Development and the Single European Market" - Sam Aaronovitch
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "The New Municipal Socialism" - Geoff Green
- August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Adult Education and Training for Local Economic Development" - Marjorie Mayo, prepared for Great Lakes Economic Development Group Conference on Responses to Economic Restructuring
- September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  "Urban Development Corporations: The Docklands Experiment" - Bob Colenutt, paper for Conference on Economic Regeneration in Chicago, Sept. 1990
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Transcript of talk given by John Bennington at Sheffield Conference
- Various. Various Papers and Working Papers on Economic Development - cont'd, March 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "New Urban Institutions: City Governance and the Retreat of Public Policy" - Robin Boyle and Paul Lawless (draft)
- July 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "A Proposal to Establish a Centre for Active Citizenship Based at Fircroft College - Birmingham" - Author Unknown
- Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "Urban Development Corporation and the Regional Plannin in the UK: The Impact of the Black Country Development Corporation" - Alan Middleton, Patrick Loftman, Brendan Nevin
- November 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "Multinational Capital, National States, and Local Communities" - Manuel Castells (working paper)
- November 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "The Politics of Empowerment in the UK" - Gary Craig
- February 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  "Locality and Local State: Sheffield's Economic Policy" - Mark Goodwin (working paper)
- Various. CDP Articles; scholarly articles, journals, pamphlets, reports, late 1970s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Miscellaneous; 40 items
- T Young. Thesis submitted for University of Sussex; Central Initiatives at the Local Level: The National Community Development Project, late 1970s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Three chapters of a thesis
- Samuel H. Bailie. Reports and articles of Oldham CDP, late 1970s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Miscellaneous; 5 items and final report
- Marjorie Mayo. Marjorie Mayo: Unpublished CDP Material, late 1970s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Miscellaneous; 13 items; reports and studies of CDP from central perspective
- Various. Early 1970s CDP documents, early 1970s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Miscellaneous; 28 items; correspondence, reports, commentaries
- Various. CDP-North Tyneside, late 1970s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Miscellaneous: 11 items; reports, booklets, handwritten notes, pamphlets
- Various. CDP Central Papers 1969-1970, early 1970s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  22 items: Meeting minutes; memos; memoranda
- Various. CDP Central Material 1973-1978, Mid-1970s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  49 items: Handwritten notes; correspondence; reports;meeting minutes
- Various. Newcastle CDP; reports, pamphlets, booklets, interviews; handwritten notes; Worker's Chronicle publication; correspondence, late 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Miscellaneous; 31 items